trustnet.com 2015-10-06

# Privacy Policy | FE Trustnet

**FE TRUSTNET PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY**

Financial Express (Holdings) Limited (“we”, “our”, “us” and derivatives) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Use, sets out the basis on which any personal data that we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us relating to your use of the FE Trustnet site (“site”). 

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is Trustnet Limited of 2nd Floor, Golden House, 30 Great Pulteney Street, London, W1F 9NN. Our nominated representative for the purpose of this Act is Kirsty Witter. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?**  
We collect information about you when you register with us or use the site. When you access the FE Trustnet portfolio tool, we ask you to register and set up a user name and password, and to enter details of your investments, numbers of shares or units and other personal information. E-mail addresses are required in order to register for some features of the site. 

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your operating system, browser version, domain name and IP address and details of the website that you came from, in order to improve this site. 

Further, Money Laundering legislation requires that we obtain information so as to verify your identity. 

You confirm that all information you supply is accurate. 

**COOKIES**  
In order to provide personalised services to and analyse site traffic, we may use a cookie file which is stored on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Some of the cookies we use are essential for the site to operate. When you are asked to select an investor type, we make a record of your choice and put a cookie on your computer to ensure that you receive content which is designated to suit your requirements and complies with the rules set down by the Financial Conduct Authority about the type of information we can supply to different types of investor. 

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or part of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our site. 

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION**   
We store and use information you provide as follows: 

  * to present content effectively;
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which may interest you, tailored to your specific interests, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts between you and us;
  * to enable you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * to improve our content by tracking group information that describes the habits, usage, patterns and demographics of our customers.

We may also send you emails to provide information and keep you up to date with developments on our site. It is our policy to have instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future e-mails. You can change your e-mail address at any time.

In order to provide support on the usage of the FE Trustnet portfolio tool, our support team need access to all information provided in relation to this tool.

We will not disclose your name, email address or postal address or any data that could identify you to any third party without first receiving your permission.

However, you agree that we may disclose to any regulatory authority to which we are subject and to any investment exchange on which we may deal or to its related clearing house (or to investigators, inspectors or agents appointed by them), or to any person empowered to require such information by or under any legal enactment, any information they may request or require relating to you, or if relevant, any of your clients.

You agree that we may pass on information obtained under Money Laundering legislation as we consider necessary to comply with reporting requirements under such legislation.

If you do not want us to use your data in these ways, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

**ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND CORRECTION**  
We want to ensure that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information that is inaccurate.

You have the right under data protection legislation to access information held about you. If you wish to receive a copy of any personal information we hold, please write to us at 3rd Floor, Hollywood House, Church Street East, Woking, GU21 6HJ. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, amongst other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary, including the use of encryption, to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. You will not hold us responsible for any breach of security unless we have been negligent or in wilful default. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. 

**OTHER WEBSITES**  
Our site contains links to other websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**CONTACT**  
If you want more information or have any questions or comments relating to our privacy policy please email [publishing@financialexpress.net](mailto:publishing@financialexpress.net?subject=Trustnet%20United%20Kingdom%20Privacy%20Cookie%20Policy) in the first instance.
